Guide to the Cass Gilbert Papers and Architectural Drawings 1883-1952 (Bulk 1900-1934) PR 21
New-York Historical Society
- Series X. Architectural Drawings, 1883-1952
  - PR21.414: Unidentified Monument, 1896
    - Study. graphite and paint on board, 1931 January (Object PR21.414.O1)
  - PR21.415: Unidentified Tomb (Newark, N.J.)
    - Perspective study. graphite and watercolor. (Object PR21.415.O1)
  - PR21.416: Eglise St Pierre le Puellier (Orleans, France) - from sketchbook, not a CG project, 1880
    - Tracing from sketchbook. ink on trace and board., 1880 (Object PR21.416.O1)
  - PR21.417: Unidentified Building (Beauvais, France) - travel sketch, not a CG project
    - Sketch of doorway. ink on paper and board., 1880 (Object PR21.417.O1)
  - PR21.418 Elmer Gerry Law Library (not CG; Alfred Zucker, Architect), 1896
    - Interior perspective study. graphite and watercolor on paper and board. (Object PR21.418.O1)
  - PR21.419: Material not produced by Cass Gilbert
    - New York skyscrapers from Jersey City, (Irving Underhill). photograph on board., 1908 (Object PR21.419.O1)
    - Madison Square Garden (McKim, Mead, and White), folded drawings (Offsite-box CG-12)
  - [not CG] Providence Biltmore Hotel (Providence, R.I.)
    - Folded drawings: blueprints (Offsite-box CG-194)
  - [not CG] James Weed Store Building (Saint Paul, Minn.)